<resources>
    <string name="app_name">
        <b>
            <h3>FitBit</h3>
        </b>
    </string>
    <string name="register">New here?
        <b>Register</b>
    </string>
    <string name="login">Already have account? Login</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="Pullup">A classic pullup involves gripping an overhead bar and using your upper body strength to raise
        your body until your chin is above the bar. \n

        <b>\n To perform the Pullup:</b>\n \n
        1. Position yourself on the pullup bar using an overhand grip that’s slightly wider than your shoulders.\n \n
        2. Make firm grip and pull your body upwards so that your chin is just above the bar. \n \n
        3. Slowly lower your body back down to the starting position.\n \n

        Since pullups are a compound exercise, they use multiple joints and muscles. Pullups use your lats and biceps
        primarily,
        while also recruiting your deltoids, rhomboids, and core. These are the muscles you’ll need to strengthen.\n \n

        <b>\n The benefits of pullups include : great muscle growth and fat loss ,improved grip strength ,enhanced
            fitness ability ,enhanced mental health.
        </b>
        \n
    </string>


    <string name="Squats">The squat movement pattern primarily trains the following muscles: quadriceps , gluteus
        maximus ,
        calves , hamstrings.\n\n

        <b>To perform the bodyweight squat:</b>
        \n \n
        1. Stand with your feet around
        shoulder-width apart and turned out 5–12 degrees.\n \n
        2. Begin the motion by moving your hips backward, sitting back,
        and lowering your hips. Reach your arms out in front for counterbalance. \n \n
        3.As you sit back, generate tension in your feet and legs by imagining you’re pushing your knees outward and
        sitting down between your thighs, as
        opposed to on top of them. This is to counteract the tendency to let your knees cave or turn inward. \n \n
        4. Lower your hips until the tops of your thighs are parallel to the floor. You can go lower if your mobility
        allows. \n \n
        5. Once you reach the bottom position, push through each foot evenly to stand up to the starting position.\n \n
        <b>The Benefits of doing squats Strengthens your core Calorie burning Strengthens the muscles of your lower body
            Boosts athletic ability
            and strength
        </b>
        \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="Pushup">Traditional pushups are beneficial for building upper body strength. \n \n
        <b>To perform pushup:</b>
        \n \n
        1. Start kneeling on an exercise mat or the floor and bring your feet
        together behind you. \n \n
        2. Keep your back straight and your core engaged. \n \n
        3. Your butt should be down, not lifted. \n \n
        4. Your body should form a straight line. Don’t arch your back or let your body sag down. \n \n
        5. Bend forward to position yourself in a high plank, the top of a pushup position, with your palms flat on the
        mat, hands shoulder-width
        apart, and with your fingers facing forward or hands turned slightly in. Your shoulders should be positioned
        over your hands. Your feet should be together behind you and your back should be flat. Keep your abs pulled in.
        \n \n
        6. Slowly lower your body toward the floor. Maintain a rigid torso and keep your head aligned with your spine.
        Don’t let your low back sag or your hips hike upward. \n \n
        7. Continue to lower yourself until your chest or chin touch
        the ground. Your elbows may flare out during the downward movement. \n \n
        8. Press upward with your arms. Continue
        pressing until your arms are fully extended at your elbows, and you’re back in the plank, at the top of the
        pushup position. \n \n

        <b>The Benefits of doing pushups every day: Traditional pushups are beneficial for building upper body strength.
            They work the triceps,
            pectoral muscles, and shoulders. They can also strengthen the lower back and core by engaging (pulling in)
            the
            abdominal muscles.
        </b>
    </string>
    <string name="Bicep">Your biceps, is a double-headed muscle that runs from your shoulder to your elbow. It’s the key
        muscle involved in lifting and pulling with your arms. \n \n
        <b>To perform the Bicep :</b>
        \n \n
        1. Hold a dumbbell in each hand, with your arms down by your sides. \n \n
        2. Inhale. As you exhale, slowly curl the weights up toward your shoulders. \n \n
        3. Focus on using your biceps to pull the weights up. Don’t sway, lean forward, or arch your back as you bring
        them up. Keep your core engaged and your back straight. \n \n
        4. Pause, then lower the dumbbells to the starting position.\n \n \n

        <b>Concentration curls</b>
        \n \n

        people ages 18 to 24, the concentration curl is the most effective exercise for isolating and strengthening your
        biceps. \n \n

        <b>To perform the Concentration curls:</b>
        \n \n

        1. Sit on a bench or chair with your legs apart, lean forward slightly.\n \n
        2. Pick up a dumbbell with your left hand and rest your elbow against the inside of your left thigh. This is the
        starting position.\n \n
        3. With your palm facing up, slowly curl the dumbbell toward your shoulder.\n \n
        4. Pause, then slowly lower the weight to the starting position.\n \n
        5. After you do a set with your left arm, do the same with your right arm.
    </string>
    <string name="Abs">
        <b>Crunches
            It targets the rectus abdominis, or your six-pack muscles.
        </b>
        \n \n
        <b>To perform the Crunches :</b>
        \n \n
        1. Lie on your back on a mat, knees bent, feet on the floor, and arms crossed over your chest. Ensure your neck
        stays untucked
        throughout the movement. \n \n
        2. Using your abs, begin to roll your head, neck, and shoulder blades up off the ground.\n \n
        3. Pause when you reach the top, then slowly lower back down. \n \n
        4. Complete 15–20 reps for 3 sets. \n \n
        <b>Bicycle crunches</b>
        The squat movement pattern primarily trains the following muscles: obliques and rectus abdominis — those
        six-pack muscles — with bicycle crunches. \n \n
        <b>To perform the Bicycle crunches :</b>
        \n \n
        1. Assume tabletop position with your knees bent at a 90-degree angle and fingers interlaced behind your head.
        \n \n
        2. Crunch up and rotate, bringing your right elbow to your left knee and allowing your right leg to extend.\n \n
        3. Return your right elbow and right leg to the starting position, immediately crunching back up to bring your
        left elbow to your
        right knee and extending your left leg.\n \n
        4. Complete 20 reps total (10 on each side) for 3 sets. \n \n
        <b>Leg raises</b>
        \n \n
        This is a more challenging exercise. Be aware that leg raises can easily cause your lower back to creep off the
        ground
        to help you compensate. Focus on recruiting your abs to do the work. \n \n
        <b>To perform the Leg raises :</b>
        \n \n
        1. Lie on your back on a mat, arms down by your sides and palms on the ground or underneath your butt for extra
        support.\n \n
        2. Recruit your core to lift your legs straight up until your body forms a 90-degree angle. \n \n
        3. Slowly lower your legs back down to the ground.\n \n
        4. Complete 10 reps for 3 sets. \n \n
        By just focusing on three exercises per week for one month, the best ab workout is simple and effective.
    </string>

    <string name="jumpingrope">The act of jumping rope relies on your lower body muscles calves, thighs, and buttocks,
        upper body shoulders and biceps, and abdominal muscles \n
        <b>To perform the jumping rope :</b>
        \n \n
        1. Before you begin using a rope, measure it to your height. When you stand on the middle of the rope, the
        handles should extend to your armpits. \n \n
        2. Hold the rope with hands at about hip height and elbows slightly bent, keeping your upper arms close to your
        sides. Your chest should be out and your shoulders back and down. Make your jumps small and land on the balls of
        your feet. \n \n \n \n \n \n \n\n

    </string>
    <string name="vegbowl">
        <br>Paneer 50gm ,</br>
        <br>Some grain: rice / millets , \n</br>
        <br>Some protein: dal / beans / peanuts / sattu ,</br>
        \n
        <br>Some cooked vegetables , \n</br>
        <br>Crunchy toppings: raw salad \n</br>

        <br></br>

        <br>\n Cook everything on low flame. \n \n</br>

        <b>Protein Values :</b>
        \n  <br></br>50gm Panner Protein 22g ,\n
        <br></br>
        50gm dal Protein 12.9g , \n
        <br></br>
        50gm dal peanuts 13 g


    </string>
    <string name="nonvegbowl">
        <br>50 gm chicken breasts, \n</br>
        <br>1/2 cup boiled chickpeas, \n</br>
        <br>1/2 cup boiled rice, \n</br>
        <br>50gm cheese, \n</br>
        <br>4 Eggs \n \n</br>
        <br></br>
        <b>Protein Values :\n</b>
        50 gm chicken has 14 grams of protein \n
        <br></br>
        1/2 cup boiled chickpeas has 10 grams of protein \n
        <br></br>
        1/2 cup boiled rice has 2 grams of protein \n
        <br></br>
        50gm cheese has 13 grams of protein \n
        <br></br>
        4 Eggs has 24 grams of protein \n
        <br></br>


    </string>


</resources>